<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Adhy Setiawan</title>
    <link>http://www.adhysetiawan.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Adhy Setiawan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 16:42:36 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.adhysetiawan.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>BTW I use Arch</title>
      <link>http://www.adhysetiawan.com/posts/arch/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 16:42:36 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.adhysetiawan.com/posts/arch/</guid>
      <description>Note: this is a work in progress. Part 1: Arch installation 0. Preparation Resize the partition using windows disk utility. Allocate some free space for arch.
1. Downloading the image and create an installation media 1.1. Download https://download.nus.edu.sg/mirror/archlinux/iso/2022.10.01/ Download archlinux-x86_64.iso and archlinux-x86_64.iso.sig
Verify the key
gpg --keyserver-options auto-key-retrieve --verify archlinux-x86_64.iso.sig Confirm that the key fingerprint is shown at the the Developer page of arch.
1.2. Create media Insert USB Get the USB device name from</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WiFi craking - WPA2 Personal</title>
      <link>http://www.adhysetiawan.com/posts/wifi-cracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.adhysetiawan.com/posts/wifi-cracking/</guid>
      <description>Table of Content Background WPA2 PSK PTK and the Four-way Handshake MIC (the weakness to be exploited) PMKID (other method to crack PSK) Tools Steps Hash cracking hxcpcapng Heuristics References WPA2 PSK PMKID Hash cracking Background WPA2 PSK (Personal) Wireless Protected Access 2 (WPA2) is a standard established by the IEEE to secure wireless communication. PSK stands for Pre-Shared Key, meaning both the access point and the user knows a secret shared even before they establish a connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Burp Suite</title>
      <link>http://www.adhysetiawan.com/posts/intro-to-burp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.adhysetiawan.com/posts/intro-to-burp/</guid>
      <description>What is Burp Suite? Burp is all-in-one platform for website security testing. It has a variety of tools, such as:
Proxy to intercept, inspect, and modify HTTP requests A repeater to easily edit and re-send HTTP requests An &amp;ldquo;intruder&amp;rdquo; to send multiple requests (one use case is to brute-force a login page) Text encoder/decoder (HTML, URL, Base64, etc.) Why Burp Suite? When we are doing security testing, we want to give the application (lots of) unusual inputs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
